<dialog>
  <page tag="start">...</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>That was fast!</page>
      <page tag ="Info">What's next?</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>...</page>
      <page> Adjusting...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>We have arrived in Baghdad circa 800 CE! </page>
      <say>Circa? You mean you don't know exactly?</say>
      <page>I mean...</page>
      <page>Not entirely...</page>
      <say>ALPHA!!</say>
      <page>The farther we go back, the harder it is for me to get my dates perfectly right! Lay off!</page>
      <page>I'm just a simple highly sophisticated artificial intelligence!</page>
      <page>At any rate, you're here to see Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi.</page>
      <page>He contributed tremendously to the fields of mathematics and geography.</page>
      <page>At this moment, he is working in the House of Wisdom most days.</page>
      <page>However, we've landed in a district near the outskirts of Baghdad where you will be able to find his workshop.</page>
      <advance/>
      <page>Can I help you with anything else?</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-5/Leave/0">
    <true>
      <page>Did you learn enough from Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi?</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>Yes. </say>
          <page>I call that a success! </page>
          <page>Are you ready to leave?</page>
          <reply>
            <option>
              <say>Not yet.</say>
              <page>Okay, just let me know when you're ready.</page>
              <finish/>
            </option>
            <option>
              <say>Yes!</say>
              <page>Then let us be off!</page>
              <page>Who is next?</page>
              <say>Let's see...</say>
              <say>Murasaki Shikibu.</say>
              <page>Away we go!</page>
              <advance/>
              <finish/>
            </option>
          </reply>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Not yet.</say>
          <page>Well then, get to it!</page>
          <finish/>
        </option>
      </reply>
    </true>
  </if>
  <reply>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi. </say>
      <page>al-Khwarizmi is perhaps most famous for a very popular mathematical rule set of symbol manipulation.</page>
      <page>You call it “algebra,” stemming from the Arabic “al-jabr,” which means “reunion of broken parts” or “restoration”.</page>
      <page>al-Khwarizmi's name was actually Latinized and became part of the word “algorithm.”</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about the House of Wisdom. </say>
      <page>The House of Wisdom was an intellectual center that arose during the Islamic Golden Age.</page>
      <page>The House of Wisdom included a society of scientists and academics.</page>
      <page>These scientists and academics contributed to mathematics, engineering, astronomy, and physics--to name a few.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Never mind.</say>
      <page>Sure, sure.</page>
      <finish/>
    </option>
  </reply>
</dialog>