<dialog>
  <page tag="start">Hello!</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>After you pick your book up go and talk to your TA in the cafe. It's directly east of the dorms!</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>I'm the dorm RA!</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_0-1/TalkingToRA/0">
    <true>
      <page>Do you have any classes today?</page>
      <say>Yeah, Intro to Research. </say>
      <page>I had that class my first year here. It was a lot of fun!</page>
      <page>I’d recommend getting started on your paper early though...</page>
      <page>Did you already pick up the textbook for the class?</page>
      <say>No, they were all sold out at the bookstore! </say>
      <page>I hate it when that happens! I have a solution though!</page>
      <page>Before you head off to class, stop by the library and check out the textbook. They will lend it to you for the quarter!</page>
      <page>The librarian at the front desk can help you find it!</page>
      <page>Remember, the library is directly north of the dorms.</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <page tag ="Help">Can I help you with anything?</page>
  <reply>
    <option>
      <say>Where is the library? </say>
      <page>Oh, the library is out past the quad. It’s pretty much straight north of here.</page>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Where is the coffee shop? </say>
      <page>The cafe is directly east of here.</page>
      <page>The TA for your class will be in the coffee shop, if he’s not in the classroom.</page>
      <page>Maybe get yourself some coffee or tea from the coffee shop.</page>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Where is the lecture hall? </say>
      <page>The classroom you’re looking for is… Well, go out into the quad and head right. Can’t miss it! Just about straight north-east from here.</page>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Nope.  </say>
      <page>Okay! Just stop by if you have any other questions then.</page>
      <finish/>
    </option>
  </reply>
  <goto tag="Help"/>
</dialog>
