<dialog>
  <page tag="start">Yes?</page>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/TalkBlue/0">
    <true>
      <say>I've been told that you're leaving for battle soon?</say>
      <page>Yeah, we'd have left by now if it weren't for that gate being blocked...</page>
      <page>Why do you care?</page>
      <say>Lady Murasaki wanted me to help resolve the situation between you and your brother.</say>
      <say>Is there anything you can tell me about your feud? </say>
      <page>Not much I'm afraid...</page>
      <page>It started when we were just boys...</page>
      <page>But now it's gone on for so long that I don't even know how to talk to him any more. </page>
      <page>I don't know the man he has become. </page>
      <page>But I don't want to leave and never return without first making amends with him. </page>
      <page>It's funny...</page>
      <page>On the battlefield, I'm as fierce as a tiger. </page>
      <page>But when it comes to family, I lack the courage to even talk to my own brother.</page>
      <page>Will you invite him in here for me so I can begin to mend our relationship?</page>
      <page>It's time that I swallow my pride and speak to him again.</page>
      <say>Sure, do you know where your brother is?</say>
      <page>Hmm, let me think...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>The last time I saw him he was near the west side of the front gate.</page>
      <page>He wears the loudest red armor you ever did see.</page>
      <say>I'm on it!</say>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/ReturnToBlue/0">
    <true>
      <page>Did you speak to my brother?</page>
      <page>What did he say?</page>
      <say>I explained how you felt, and he said he would be joining you shortly.</say>
      <page>Splendid!</page>
      <page>Thank you for helping me with this. </page>
      <page>At least now I can have the peace of mind that if I don't return, I can rest easy.</page>
      <page>Thank you again, friend.</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
</dialog>