<dialog>
  <page>What are you looking at...</page>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_2-8/TalkToShady/0">
    <true>
      <say>Listen, I know what you've been doing...</say>
      <page>Oh do you now?</page>
      <say>Yes...</say>
      <say>And frankly it's appalling.</say>
      <say>You don't have to live this life of crime!</say>
      <page>Now why's that...</page>
      <say>Well... you can do anything you put your mind to!</say>
      <page>Even... like, catching a thief?</page>
      <say>Exactly!</say>
      <say>Wait...</say>
      <say>What?</say>
      <page>Listen kid, I'm undercover.</page>
      <page>I'm investigating these thefts, but you're about to blow my cover...</page>
      <say>What??</say>
      <say>Do you know who the thief is?</say>
      <page>I have a hunch, but I need help following a lead.</page>
      <page>You see, everyone here think's I'm the thief, so no one will talk to me.</page>
      <page>But I've tracked the thief to this well--it seems to be where he stores the smaller goods he steals.</page>
      <page>With it being dried up and all, no one thinks to check it out.</page>
      <page>But nothing can escape my watchful eye!</page>
      <say>What can I do to help?</say>
      <page>Well, you see, everyone in this area has reported a theft.</page>
      <page>Everyone, that is, except for the wealthiest family in town.</page>
      <page>I'm thinking they're paying off the thief to keep from being stolen from.</page>
      <page>But it's impossible to prove unless I confront them.</page>
      <page>That's where you come in. </page>
      <page>I need you to go to their house, located just west of the market, and confront them about who they've been paying off.</page>
      <page>Do you think you can handle it?</page>
      <say>I'm on it!</say>
      <page>Great, great.</page>
      <page>After you find out who the thief is, confront them and I'll take it from there.</page>
      <page>I'm counting on you kid.</page>
      <page>Now, pretend like we never spoke or you'll blow my cover...</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
</dialog>