<dialog>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_3-9/Goodbye/0">
    <true>
      <page>Well, here we are... just as I promised.</page>
      <say>You know, I don't really think you're all that dangerous.</say>
      <say>I don't know why they had to shut down the lab...</say>
      <page>That's what I've been asking myself all these years!</page>
      <page>The very least they could have done was turn this into some academic amusement park for students or something...</page>
      <say>I know! I had such a blast!</say>
      <page>Oh stop, you're making me blush!</page>
      <say>Honestly though!</say>
      <say>I've had a bucket list for as long as I can remember, and thanks to you, I got to check off quite a few entries.</say>
      <say>To think, I burnt myself out trying to get good grades all through high school just so I could get into a good university like this...</say>
      <say>Just so I could graduate, get a good job, and be able to afford traveling around the world!</say>
      <say>What a waste...</say>
      <page>Hey now, if it weren't for your hard work then you wouldn't have been able to get into this university!</page>
      <page>Then you wouldn't have been able to go on that adventure with me!</page>
      <say>Woah...</say>
      <say>So is all of this an analogy for all the places education can take you?!</say>
      <page>What?</page>
      <say>What?</say>
      <page>Anyway, did you enjoy your time?</page>
      <say>Absolutely!</say>
      <say>Seeing the excitement, passion, and eagerness of all the people I met makes me want to become a researcher too!</say>
      <page>You're pulling my leg...</page>
      <say>I'm not!</say>
      <say>You really changed the way I see the world!</say>
      <page>Hey you stop it now!</page>
      <page>This is waaaay too sappy for me.</page>
      <say>You're going to miss me! I know it!</say>
      <page>Not a chance!</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>You're going to visit me, right?</page>
      <say>...</say>
      <say>Of course I will!</say>
      <page>... promise?</page>
      <say>Hey, I hear there a lot of papers that you have to write--I can't go back to Google now that I can just visit the past!</say>
      <say>Our adventures are far from over.</say>
      <page>Sure, sure.</page>
      <page>Alright, you get out of this basement and go become the researcher you want to be!</page>
      <say>I'm on it!</say>
      <say>See you soon!</say>
      <advance/>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>I'm not crying, I'm just chopping onions for a lasagna...</page>
      <page>... for one.</page>
    </false>
  </if>
</dialog>