<dialog>
  <page>Hello?</page>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_3-9/TalkToSD/0">
    <true>
      <say>Hello, are you currently working with the “Intro to Research” professor?</say>
      <page>I am, I'm one of her research assistants.</page>
      <say>I'm interested in becoming one too!</say>
      <page>Oh, that’s ambitious...</page>
      <page>Especially for a freshman like you!</page>
      <say>True, true... But I’m willing to put the time and effort.</say>
      <say>I really want to get involved, and I’ve been trying to email professors asking for positions.</say>
      <page>Let me guess, no luck?</page>
      <say>Exactly...</say>
      <page>That's fairly common.</page>
      <page>Well, I can only speak from my own experience.</page>
      <page>I actually didn’t get a research position until my third year.</page>
      <page>So yeah, patience is a key here. But let me tell you what I did right that I did wrong my first two years.</page>
      <page>First of all, if you’re emailing them, keep it professional. You know how to send email right?</page>
      <say>I just learned that!</say>
      <page>Perfect.</page>
      <page>Second, show them your skills, experience, and capabilities. Now this is a bit tricky in your case, since you literally just got here. </page>
      <say>Does that mean it’s impossible?</say>
      <page>I never said that! Actually, there were two students when I got my first research position. The second student was actually freshman!</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>Woah! Was she super genius?</say>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Don’t tell me she’s the professor’s daughter...</say>
        </option>
      </reply>
      <page>You'd think...</page>
      <page>She didn't have any previous experience but her passion was convincing enough to get the professor to select her!</page>
      <page>The student showed her seriousness and how much she was willing to work.</page>
      <page>Also, sometimes some professors actually likes hiring freshman. </page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>What?!</say>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Impossible.</say>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>No way.</say>
        </option>
      </reply>
      <page>It allows for professors to have more time to train the students. </page>
      <page>If they stay longer, by the time they’re junior, they have both the skills and a deeper knowledge of the professor's work.</page>
      <page>That can actually save tons of time for preparation!</page>
      <say>I didn't know that! </say>
      <page>Now you do!</page>
      <say>Thank you so much! I really appreciate it! You brightened my day!</say>
      <page>Sure thing. Keep going. Don’t give up!</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>Oh, it's you!</page>
      <page>Keep going. Don’t give up!</page>
      <say>I won’t! Thanks!</say>
    </false>
  </if>
</dialog>
