<dialog>
  <page tag="start">I will see you tomorrow in class.</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <false>
      <page>Good luck with your paper. </page>
      <say>I've actually almost finished my paper!</say>
      <page>Have you?!</page>
      <page>I just assigned that a few hours ago!</page>
      <page>Most students wait until the last week of class to scramble and finish the assignment.</page>
      <page>I'm actually impressed!</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_3-9/TalkToPF/0">
    <true>
      <say>I was actually wondering if I could apply for your research assistant position.</say>
      <page>Oh really?</page>
      <page>You know that these are generally for upperclassmen...</page>
      <say>I know, but I would like to try for it anyways.</say>
      <page>Hmm...</page>
      <page>I’m worried that this may get in the way of your other classes.</page>
      <say>I've almost already finished my paper for your class. Would you like to see the draft?</say>
      <page>Yeah, you said that earlier.</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>You seem to be very eager, which is something I look for in my research assistants.</page>
      <page>Alright. You have proved that you have good qualities, but it will take a little bit more than that.</page>
      <page>Here is a quiz about the world of research. Quickly fill it out and we'll talk.</page>
      <say>Thank you, professor</say>
      <say>Hmm... It has 10 questions.</say>
      <say>These don’t seem so bad.</say>
      <say>...</say>
      <say>Uh oh.</say>
      <say>...</say>
      <say>A couple of these I don’t know at all.</say>
      <say>...</say>
      <page>Don’t give up hope now.</page>
      <page>Are you finished with my quiz?</page>
      <say>Yes.</say>
      <page>Wonderful, let me take a look.</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Good, good.</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>I see that I couldn’t fool you with that question.</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>You answered the questions correctly!</page>
      <page>Tell me, how did you out the answer to the last one?</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>I already knew it.</say>
          <page>Really? You are pretty smart, then.</page>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>I looked it up.</say>
          <page>Really? Honesty is a good trait. To be fair, there is a lot I look up as well.</page>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>I guessed.</say>
          <page>Ha! I doubt that, but having a sense of humor is a good thing.</page>
        </option>
      </reply>
      <page>Anyway, I will have to think about giving you the position.</page>
      <page>I don’t think I am going to be able to use you, though...</page>
      <page>As I must consider upperclassmen first.</page>
      <say>I understand...</say>
      <say>Thanks, though.</say>
      <page>Good luck with your other applications. I will email you with my response after I review the other applicants.</page>
      <page>You've done what you can for today. You should head to your dorm room and get some rest.</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <page>Now where are my notes...</page>
</dialog>