<dialog>
  <page tag="start">...</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>You’re back! I was bored in this closet.</page>
      <page tag ="Info">What's next?</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Calibrating...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Yes... Here we are.</page>
      <page>Welcome to Tsarist Russia!</page>
      <page>If I’m not mistaken, we’ve landed in the mid 1820s.</page>
      <page>This appears to be some sort of Palace! I wonder whose it is!</page>
      <say>Um, ALPHA..?</say>
      <page>Look at the baroque style! I’ve never seen it in person before!</page>
      <say>ALPHA!</say>
      <page>Even for a closet this is luxurious!</page>
      <say>Focus!!</say>
      <page>Ah...</page>
      <page>Pardon me...</page>
      <page>Yes, Alexander Pushkin. Let’s see.</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Oooh, it seems like Nikolai Gogol is here too!</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Hmm, I’m not getting a clear coordinate from my scans.</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>I think it has something to do with all this gold leaf on the walls!</page>
      <say>...</say>
      <page>It might just be better to ask around and track down Alexander Pushkin the old fashioned way.</page>
      <page>Can I help you with anything else?</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-3/TalkToALPHA/0">
    <true>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-3/Leave/0">
    <true>
      <page>Have you gathered enough information about Alexander Pushkin?</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>Yes. </say>
          <page>Great. </page>
          <page>Are you ready to leave?</page>
          <reply>
            <option>
              <say>Not yet.</say>
              <page>I'll be here checking the gold leaf then...</page>
              <finish/>
            </option>
            <option>
              <say>Yes!</say>
              <page>Let's get going then!</page>
              <page>It looks like the next stop on our trip is to Michigan some time in the 1940s!</page>
              <page>Firing up the time machine.</page>
              <page>...</page>
              <page>All systems go!</page>
              <page>...</page>
              <advance/>
            </option>
          </reply>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Not yet.</say>
          <page>Well then, get to it!</page>
          <finish/>
        </option>
      </reply>
    </true>
  </if>
  <reply>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about Alexander Pushkin. </say>
      <page>Alexander Pushkin was a Russian poet, playwright, and novelist. Many even attribute him to being the founder of modern Russian literature!</page>
      <page>Born into Russian nobility in Moscow on May 26, 1799; Alexander Pushkin’s work defined the very language particular to Russian literature that came after him.</page>
      <page>When the Russian language failed in being able to convey ideas or emotions, Alexander Pushkin wasn’t afraid to borrow from other languages.</page>
      <page>These loanwords gave his writing an incredibly sensitive style and  expanded the Russian lexicon.</page>
      <page>Although he died at the age of 37, his work shaped and defined Russian literature in innumerable ways.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about Nikolai Gogol. </say>
      <page>Nikolai Gogol, a Russian dramatist, was born on March 31st, 1809 in what is now modern Ukraine. </page>
      <page>Often times illustrating differences between Russian and Ukrainian culture, Nikolai Gogol became an accomplished, if not unconventional, satirist.</page>
      <page>As a long time pupil, and eventual successor of Alexander Pushkin, Nikolai Gogol established a reputation as one of - if not the greatest author of prose in the Russian language.</page>
      <page>Nikolai Gogol’s works continued to contribute to Russian literature far beyond the scope of his life.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Never mind.</say>
      <page>Sure, sure. I’ll be keeping out of sight as I conduct some research on all this gold leaf.</page>
      <finish/>
    </option>
  </reply>
</dialog>
