<dialog>
  <page tag="start">...</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>You’re back! I was getting lonely.</page>
      <page tag ="Info">What can I help you with?</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>Adjusting…</page>
      <page>…</page>
      <page>Calibrating…</page>
      <page>Hmm. Yes. Okay.</page>
      <page>We have successfully traveled to an American University in the Midwest. Michigan, I believe.</page>
      <page>I am unable to assess the exact current date… as we landed in what appears to be some sort of a dilapidated closet… again.</page>
      <page>If I had to assume, based on an extremely mathematical analysis, I would say that the current date is at some point in the 1940s.</page>
      <page>Never mind that box over there that says DOCUMENTS - 1943.</page>
      <page>My scans are showing multiple lifeforms—carbon based. That’s a good sign.</page>
      <page>According to your assignment, we’re here so you can learn about Katharine Briggs and Isabel Briggs Myers and their Myers-Briggs Type Indicator test.</page>
      <page>I’m an INTP type, what are you?</page>
      <say>I… I don’t know.</say>
      <page>What a shame… You should take the test sometime.</page>
      <page>Well, let’s not waste time. Go and find Katharine Briggs.</page>
      <page>As always, if you have any questions just ask.</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-4/TalkToALPHA/0">
    <true>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-4/Leave/0">
    <true>
      <page>Have you gathered enough information about Katharine Briggs and Isabel Briggs Myers?</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>Yes. </say>
          <page>Great. </page>
          <page>Are you ready to leave?</page>
          <reply>
            <option>
              <say>Not yet.</say>
              <page>I'll be here checking my circuitry then...</page>
              <finish/>
            </option>
            <option>
              <say>Yes!</say>
              <page>Let's get going then!</page>
              <page>It looks like the next stop on our trip is to 9th century Baghdad.</page>
              <page>Firing up the time machine.</page>
              <page>...</page>
              <page>All systems go!</page>
              <page>...</page>
              <advance/>
            </option>
          </reply>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Not yet.</say>
          <page>Well then, get to it!</page>
          <finish/>
        </option>
      </reply>
    </true>
  </if>
  <reply>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me more about Katharine Briggs. </say>
      <page>Katharine Briggs, born January 3rd, 1875 came from a family who encouraged education in both men and women.</page>
      <page>A controversial idea at the time.</page>
      <page>Katharine Briggs went on to earn a degree in agriculture.</page>
      <page>Katharine Briggs eventually found her way to examining data from various child development and educational studies which led to her identification of 4 main personality types.</page>
      <page>When she was dissatisfied with the works of philosophers and psychologists in the attempt to establish one theory encompassing all aspects of the personality, she decided to create her own theory.</page>
      <page>This pursuit ended, however, when Katharine Briggs found the work of Carl Jung.</page>
      <page>After finding his work on personality type, Katharine Briggs introduced her daughter to Carl Jung’s work and they both focused on his ideas more in depth.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me more about Isabel Briggs Myers. </say>
      <page>Isabel Briggs Myers was born October 18th, 1897. </page>
      <page>Isabel Briggs Myers graduated from Swarthmore College in Pennsylvania.</page>
      <page>Initially, Isabel Briggs Myers wasn’t interested in the work of identifying and typing various personalities.</page>
      <page>However, once her mother, Katharine Briggs, introduced Isabel to the works of Carl Jung, Isabel saw potential.</page>
      <page>Isabel Briggs Myers implemented the ideas of Carl Jung, adding her own ideas, and created a survey.</page>
      <page>This would eventually, after 20 years of research, be known as the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator.</page>
      <page>The hope for this survey was to help people identify their personality for them to best succeed in life.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Never mind.</say>
      <page>I’ll be here. It’s not like I can go anywhere.</page>
      <finish/>
    </option>
  </reply>
</dialog>
