<dialog>
  <page tag="start">Hello!</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>I’m looking forward to chatting with Mrs. Briggs and Mrs. Briggs Myers when I get the chance.</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>Have you heard about the personality test?</page>
      <page>I’m impressed that the University is helping to provide an opportunity for Mrs. Briggs and Mrs. Briggs Myers to conduct their research.</page>
      <page>That’s what a Research University like ours is all about anyway!</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-4/TestOne/0">
    <true>
      <page>At any rate, what can I do for you?</page>
      <say>I’m here to administer the personality test. </say>
      <page>Oh wow! I’m excited to participate!</page>
      <page>I’ll take this immediately!</page>
      <page>
        <color hex="74f442">[A blank tests has been removed from your inventory]</color>
      </page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>The buzz about this personality test is too much to handle!</page>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-4/CollectTests/0">
    <true>
      <page>All finished!</page>
      <page>
        <color hex="74f442">[A completed test has been added to your inventory]</color>
      </page>
      <give item="Completed Test"/>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>Sorry I need to focus.</page>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-4/ReportResults/0">
    <true>
      <say>I’m here to report the results of your personality test. </say>
      <page>Already? Incredible!</page>
      <say>You are considered an “ENTP” type.</say>
      <say>That stands for Extraversion + Intuition + Thinking + Perceiving. </say>
      <say>You’re energetic, inventive, enthusiastic, abstract, and logical.</say>
      <say>You exceed when communicating and generating innovative ideas.</say>
      <say>However, you grow bored with projects easily and tend to be argumentative.</say>
      <page>My colleagues always say that I’m not one to shy away from an argument…</page>
      <page>I guess that’s just a side effect of passion I suppose!</page>
      <page>I have noticed the “easily bored” trait affecting my life though.</page>
      <page>It takes a lot of persistence to keep going when you’re not interested in a subject or a project, but it all pays off in the end!</page>
      <page>Thanks!</page>
      <page>
        <color hex="74f442">[This person's test results have been removed from your inventory]</color>
      </page>
      <advance/>
      <take item="Test Results"/>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>Now, where was I..?</page>
    </false>
  </if>
  <page>...</page>
</dialog>
