<dialog>
  <page tag="start">Hello there.</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <false>
      <page>It's quite a big day for me today!</page>
      <say>Are you Johannes Gutenberg? </say>
      <page>Why yes I am!</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-7/TalkToJG/0">
    <true>
      <say>Can I ask you about your work here at your forge?</say>
      <page>Yes, but can you do me a very important favor?</page>
      <say>How did I not see this coming...</say>
      <page>Huh?</page>
      <say>Nothing, nothing. What do you need?</say>
      <page>If you cross the river, in the first building after the crossing there is a shop.</page>
      <page>I am supposed to be receiving a print plate from the Master of Playing Cards from the shop today.</page>
      <page>I ordered the plate very long ago and it has finally arrived!</page>
      <page>Although, I must remain here as I'm awaiting a messenger to give word on if my bank loan was approved or not.</page>
      <say>Let me guess, I'm supposed to fetch the plate for you?</say>
      <page>If you wouldn't mind?</page>
      <say>Fine, fine. I'll get the plate for you. Then will you answer my questions?</say>
      <page>Absolutely!</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-7/ReturnToJG/0">
    <true>
      <page>Did you get the plates for me?</page>
      <say>Here they are.</say>
      <take item="Master of Playing Cards plates" count="1"/>
      <page><color hex="74f442">[The Master of Playing Cards plates have been removed from your inventory]</color></page>
      <page>Ah, I get to print these beautiful cards, but regrettably, I do not know who makes these intaglio engravings.</page>
      <say>Can you tell me more about them?</say>
      <page>Of course. Right now, we use copper plates with engravings in them.</page>
      <page>You ink the painting, use the press and you get an image.</page>
      <page>The high areas on the plate leave blank spots. The low points -filled with ink- gives you the image.</page>
      <page>It is the opposite of relief painting, where you put ink on top of high points.</page>
      <page>But enough of my rambling. I have horrible news...</page>
      <say>What happened?</say>
      <page>While you were away the messenger came by and informed me that I didn't qualify for a loan from the bank...</page>
      <page>I'm afraid I made quite a fool of myself...</page>
      <page>I'm afraid I upset the head banker, Johann Fust, quite a bit.</page>
      <page>I whipped up a set of playing cards from the Master of Playing Card plate. Can you take it to Johann Fust in the bank?</page>
      <page>I'm hoping this gift will smooth things over, and more importantly demonstrate the precision I print at.</page>
      <page>I think I can use the prints as collateral for my new invention. It is a printing press that I think will revolutionize the world, but I need money for a new workshop.</page>
      <say>Sure, I can help. Anything for a famous inventor!</say>
      <give item="Printed cards" count="1"/>
      <page><color hex="74f442">[The printed cards have been added to your inventory]</color></page>
      <page>Famous? Says who?!</page>
      <say>Never mind! Where should I be headed?</say>
      <page>The bank is across the river, up north.</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-7/FinishJG/0">
    <true>
      <page>What did mister Fust say?</page>
      <say>I gave him the cards and he said he would be by tomorrow to talk to you about the details.</say>
      <page>That is wonderful news! I will need to find a larger workshop!</page>
      <page>I already know what the first thing I will print!</page>
      <page>The Bible!</page>
      <page>They shall call it the 42-line Bible!</page>
      <say>How about the Gutenberg Bible?</say>
      <page>Even better!</page>
      <page>It will be so much faster than writing it by hand.</page>
      <page>Anyway, what was it that you wanted from me?</page>
      <say>As an inventor, do you go through any processes of review?</say>
      <page>Absolutely.</page>
      <page>I often rely on my <color hex="f47742">peers</color> in the community to test and give important feedback for various changes I’ve made to whatever I’ve been working on.</page>
      <page>Inventors in particular can make great use of like minded individuals--remember, things are seldom created completely independently.</page>
      <page>We all feed off one another until a finished product is created!</page>
      <say>What type of research does an inventor need to conduct when creating an invention?</say>
      <page>Excellent question! There are two types of research really, <color hex="f47742">primary</color> and <color hex="f47742">secondary</color>.</page>
      <page><color hex="f47742">Primary research</color> involves collecting new information that has not been gathered before.</page>
      <page>A researcher or an inventor can test their ideas on others and observe the subject’s reactions. </page>
      <page><color hex="f47742">Secondary research</color> involves collecting information that has already been produced.</page>
      <page>If a researcher knows how someone will react to a given experiment, then the inventor or researcher can better predict how their work may affect others.</page>
      <say>I was wondering if you could tell me about the importance of books?</say>
      <page>Ah, books are incredible ways for people to share their knowledge--often allowing for researcher’s ideas to survive long after they’ve passed on.</page>
      <say>Speaking of researchers, what exactly is a research journal?</say>
      <page>That’s not quite my area of expertise, you should ask the local librarian for information about that!</page>
      <page>He used to work at a University so I’m sure he can answer more of your questions than I can.</page>
      <page>Thank you again for all your help!</page>
      <page>I couldn't have done this without you!</page>
      <say>Stop, you're making me blush!</say>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <page>Please hurry along now.</page>
</dialog>
