<dialog>
  <page tag="start">Hello there.</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>I'm working on making an astrolabe.</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <say>Hello, are you Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi?</say>
      <page>I am indeed. What brings you to here?</page>
      <say>I'm just looking around.</say>
      <say>What are you working on?</say>
      <page>I'm making an astrolabe, but I'm waiting on a part from the metalsmith.</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-5/TalkToAK/0">
    <true>
      <say>I could retrieve the piece for you.</say>
      <page>Could you? That would be great!</page>
      <page>The metalsmith is at the forge in the north west part of this district.</page>
      <page>Once you retrieve the piece I can tell you more about what I'm making.</page>
      <say>On it!</say>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-5/GiveBPart/0">
    <true>
      <page>Are those the plates?</page>
      <say>Yes, they are.</say>
      <page>Wonderful! Let's have them then.</page>
      <take item="Astrolabe Plates" count="1"/>
      <page><color hex="74f442">[The Astrolabe plates have been removed from your inventory]</color></page>
      <page>Hmm...</page>
      <page>The rete on this plate seems to be...</page>
      <page>Damaged. Or misaligned at least.</page>
      <page>The engraving on one of these plates is also wrong.</page>
      <page>This won’t work for my astrolabe at all!</page>
      <page>How... disappointing.</page>
      <page>Do you know what happened?</page>
      <say>I brought them right here, the metalsmith must have messed them up somehow...</say>
      <page>That's unfortunate.</page>
      <say>Can they still be used?</say>
      <page>Now that you mention it...</page>
      <page>I think these parts can still be used to make a complete sundial.</page>
      <page>Although not what I wanted, still very useful.</page>
      <page>Just because you have broken or bad parts, it doesn't mean they are worthless.</page>
      <page>In my work with numbers and calculations, you learn to sort through piles of <color hex="f47742">non-useful information</color> for the bits you <color hex="f47742">need</color>.</page>
      <page>You can then take the data from the imprecise tools and make new, more accurate, tools--like an astrolabe!</page>
      <say>But how do you know when the tools are giving you accurate information?</say>
      <page>It can be complex, but <color hex="f47742">proofs</color> are particularly important to my field of work.</page>
      <page>They're really the last line of defense against making miscalculations.</page>
      <page>We also rely on multiple tools, and multiple people taking data.</page>
      <page>That way if there are any inconsistencies, they can be caught with relative ease.</page>
      <page>See, my peers suspected that my last astrolabemay have a small error in the plate engraving.</page>
      <page>This could have thrown off my previous calculations if not tested.</page>
      <page>Therefore, I requested to have multiple parts made for several astrolabes.</page>
      <page>I was going to test them before giving them to my colleagues to make sure my calculations were correct.</page>
      <say>What are you using the astrolabe for?</say>
      <page>I am mapping longitudes and latitudes, based on Ptolemy’s work in Geography.</page>
      <page>Based on the measurements I have already taken, I think that he has overestimated the size of the Mediterranean Sea.</page>
      <page>... Though he does give a good starting reference point to work with.</page>
      <page>To be sure, I need a correctly functioning astrolabe.</page>
      <say>Can I be of assistance?</say>
      <page>Oh wonderful!</page>
      <page>Can you return to the metalsmith and retrieve the astrolabe plates I lent to him?</page>
      <page>He was supposed to use the plates as a template, but that didn't end up working out...</page>
      <say>I'm on it!</say>
      <page>Thank you.</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-5/GiveGPart/0">
    <true>
      <page>My astrolabe plates!</page>
      <take item="Correct Astrolabe Plates" count="1"/>
      <page><color hex="74f442">[The Astrolabe plates have been removed from your inventory]</color></page>
      <page>Thank you very much!</page>
      <say>It's not a problem!</say>
      <say>Can you tell me how this astrolabe works?</say>
      <page>Absolutely!</page>
      <page>You see, the plate you just gave to me fits into the large circular groove--then I can spin the disks to predict the elliptical path of different stars.</page>
      <say>How interesting!</say>
      <say>So an astrolabe can kind of resemble a tool that <color hex="f47742">narrows</color> your search?</say>
      <page>A keen observation!</page>
      <page>Similar to searching for information in a library, or the cosmos, we need tools to <color hex="f47742">specifically hone</color> what we're looking for.</page>
      <page>Just as the astrolabe can be used to track most any stars, a library can provide resources to search <color hex="f47742">broad topics</color>.</page>
      <page>However, the astrolabe works best when they're crafted for particular stars.</page>
      <page>Kind of like how interesting fields, like mathematics, can be approached on a <color hex="f47742">subfield</color> level--like focusing on geometry!</page>
      <page>Well thank you for all of your help!</page>
      <page>Don't forget to keep searching for information and always learn as much as you can!</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <page>I am hoping to have assembled the astrolabe tonight. I want to take some measurements of the stars.</page>
</dialog>

