<dialog>
  <page tag="start">...</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>That was fast!</page>
      <page tag ="Info">What's next?</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>...</page>
      <page> Adjusting...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>We have arrived in the Heian period of Japan! </page>
      <page>From my calculations we are in either the late 10th century or the early 11th century. </page>
      <page>Somewhere around the 1000s.</page>
      <page>My visionary receptors show that we're near the Heian palace, which is in present day Kyoto, Japan!</page>
      <page>You're off to find Murasaki Shikibu.</page>
      <page>Famous author of The Tale of Genji and The Diary of Lady Murasaki.</page>
      <page>There are a lot of people here...</page>
      <page>So my scanners can't locate her exactly... </page>
      <page>But oh look! There's a book just on that table behind you.</page>
      <page>Maybe that will be of use to you?</page>
      <advance/>
      <page>Can I help you with anything else?</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/Leave/0">
    <true>
      <page>Did you learn enough from Murasaki Shikibu?</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>Yes. </say>
          <page>I call that a success! </page>
          <page>Are you ready to leave?</page>
          <reply>
            <option>
              <say>Not yet.</say>
              <page>Okay, just let me know when you're ready.</page>
              <finish/>
            </option>
            <option>
              <say>Yes!</say>
              <page>Then let us be off!</page>
              <page>Who is next?</page>
              <say>Let's see...</say>
              <say>Johannes Gutenberg.</say>
              <page>Away we go!</page>
              <advance/>
              <finish/>
            </option>
          </reply>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Not yet.</say>
          <page>Well then, get to it!</page>
          <finish/>
        </option>
      </reply>
    </true>
  </if>
  <reply>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about Murasaki Shikibu. </say>
      <page>She is regarded as the world’s first novelist, writing about the court life of Heian period Japan.</page>
      <page>Murasaki Shikibu is a pseudonym used by the writer of The Tale of Genji.</page>
      <page>Although the author's real name is unknown, many speculate that the author may have been Fujiwara no Takako.</page>
      <page>For the time period, a female writer would have been largely unheard of.</page>
      <page>Despite this, we know that Murasaki Shikibu, and other ladies of the court were taught to read and write Japanese.</page>
      <page>The Tale of Genji was most likely written for fellow members of the court to read as entertainment.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Never mind.</say>
      <page>Sure, sure.</page>
      <finish/>
    </option>
  </reply>
</dialog>