<dialog>
  <page tag="start">...</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>Hello again.</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>Oh! You surprised me.</page>
      <say>I’m sorry, I didn’t mean to!</say>
      <page>It is alright. I was just preoccupied with my writing that I didn’t notice you come in.</page>
      <say>Are you Murasaki Shikibu?</say>
      <page>You could call me that, yes.</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/TalkToMS1/0">
    <true>
      <say>What are you working on?</say>
      <page>I would call it a journal, but it is more like a story of court life.</page>
      <page>I've unfortunately misplaced one of my chapters...</page>
      <page>Now the story won't make sense unless I rewrite it.</page>
      <say>Is this what you were looking for?</say>
      <take item="Mysterious Journal" count="1"/>
      <page><color hex="74f442">[The mysterious journal has been removed from your inventory]</color></page>
      <page>Yes, that is definitely mine!</page>
      <page>Where did you find it?</page>
      <page>I've been looking all over for it.</page>
      <say>It was on a table just south of here.</say>
      <page>Oh, one of the people at court must have found it and started reading it then!</page>
      <page>My work is becoming more popular with the court, so it's getting hard to keep all of the chapters together.</page>
      <page>I never thought that my writing would be so well received, but I am humbled by the reception.</page>
      <page>You have proven to be quite resourceful at retrieving my missing chapter.</page>
      <page>Could you do me another favor?</page>
      <say>What do you need?</say>
      <page>My work on this story is almost done, but unfortunately I have lent pieces out to people of the court and I need to get them back to put the story together.</page>
      <page>Can you collect the chapters for me?</page>
      <say>Sure, where do I start?</say>
      <page>Wonderful!</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with one of the ladies in waiting here in this room.</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with one of the ladies in the tea room, just east of here.</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with one of the lords near the south gate.</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with the lord perched on the stone just south of this room.</page>
      <page>Please return if you need help locating the chapters.</page>
      <advance/>
      <finish/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/GetChapters/0">
    <true>
      <page>Have you collected my works together?</page>
      <say>Not yet.</say>
      <say>Where were the chapters again?</say>
      <page>One chapter should be with one of the ladies in waiting here in this room.</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with one of the ladies in the tea room, just east of here.</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with one of the lords near the south gate.</page>
      <page>One chapter should be with the lord perched on the stone just south of this room.</page>
      <page>Please return if you need help locating the chapters.</page>
      <finish/>
    </true>
  </if>

  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/ReturnToMS1/0">
    <true>
      <page>Have you collected my works together?</page>
      <say>Yes, here they are!.</say>
      <take item="Loose Chapters" count="4"/>
      <page><color hex="74f442">[The loose chapters have been removed from your inventory]</color></page>
      <page>Thank you very much.</page>
      <say>What are you writing about?</say>
      <page>I wanted to record the life in these courts so that others can know what it is like here and now.</page>
      <page>Court life can be unforgiving in many ways.</page>
      <page>Therefore, I can escape to different lives through my writing.</page>
      <say>Have you always been interested in writing?</say>
      <page>I suppose I have been.</page>
      <page>However, I didn't know what I wanted to write about until I spent some time thinking about it.</page>
      <page>By thinking about writing, I was able to <color hex="f47742">focus</color> on what I found was most important to me.</page>
      <page>Life is far too short to work away doing something you <color hex="f47742">don't like doing</color>, or working at something you don't find <color hex="f47742">interesting</color>.</page>
      <page>That is why it's important to <color hex="f47742">narrow your interests</color>, so you can live a more fulfilling life.</page>
      <say>That's incredibly wise!</say>
      <say>Can I ask you a few more questions?</say>
      <page>I would love to say yes...</page>
      <page>However, the calligraphers are waiting to get this manuscript so that they can begin to copy what I have written here.</page>
      <page>I need to take a few moments and make sure this is all in order.</page>
      <page>The court, however, is full of unrest.</page>
      <page>Do you think you could help one of the ladies here in this room with what bothers her?</page>
      <page>I'm finding it difficult to focus as she keeps sighing...</page>
      <say>I'm on it!</say>
      <page>Thank you so very much!</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/ReturnToMS2/0">
    <true>
      <page>Thank you for helping her!</page>
      <page>She seems incredibly ecstatic, however, I dare not ask what she was so down about.</page>
      <page>Matters of the heart are best left to the parties involved.</page>
      <say>Have you finished organizing your work?</say>
      <page>I wish I could say yes...</page>
      <page>The members of the court have reordered so many of these pages that it will take much longer than anticipated to fix this mess.</page>
      <page>If you were willing to wait, however, I have one more task for you.</page>
      <say>What needs to be done?</say>
      <page>One of the lords has been having a dispute with his brother for longer than any of us can remember.</page>
      <page>However, the lord is leaving to fight in a battle and doesn't want to leave things the way they are between the two.</page>
      <page>Could you help resolve this feud?</page>
      <say>Sure, where do I need to go?</say>
      <page>The lord in question is in the tea room, just east of here.</page>
      <page>He is the one in the rather loud blue armor, you can't miss him.</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-6/ReturnToMS3/0">
    <true>
      <page>Have the brothers stopped fighting?</page>
      <say>It has been taken care of.</say>
      <page>Wonderful!</page>
      <page>Families often squabble because they are close.</page>
      <page>We always think that there is more time, but we never know when it will be the last time we see a loved one.</page>
      <page>Keep that in mind when speaking with the ones you love.</page>
      <page>Now, I have finished reorganizing my book, and have time to chat.</page>
      <page>What were your lingering questions?</page>
      <say>You mentioned narrowing your field of interest, but what if I'm interested in doing many things?</say>
      <page>Ah, there are never enough hours in a day...</page>
      <page>A good thing to do is to identify what things you're interested in.</page>
      <page>Then, you should identify what it is about those things that interests you.</page>
      <page>By breaking up a <color hex="f47742">field</color> into more narrow <color hex="f47742">subfields</color>, you can get to the root of what it is that interests you about a given field.</page>
      <page>Once you identify all of the related subfields for a given field of work, you can <color hex="f47742">cross out the ones that don't interest you</color>.</page>
      <page>After you've specified what exactly it is that interests you, you should <color hex="f47742">find people working in that field</color>...</page>
      <page>Or examples of what it's like to work in those subfields.</page>
      <page>You can play a simple game of "who, what, where, when, and why" to further narrow interest.</page>
      <page>For example, I began writing court life down as a way to remember what was happening, to bring honor as part of my service here.</page>
      <page>Once my writing gained traction, I wrote more and more.</page>
      <page>Writing is so broad in its uses, so I decided that I wanted people to know what it is like here.</page>
      <page>I think these stories will help others see what my world is like as a lady of the court.</page>
      <say>Thank you again for your insight!</say>
      <page>It is not a problem!</page>
      <page>Thank you for settling some of the unrest here at the court!</page>
      <page>I must now be off in a moment to get these chapters to the calligraphers.</page>
      <say>Good luck!</say>
      <page>You too!</page>
      <advance/>
    </true>
  </if>
  <page>Stop by later and we can chat more.</page>
</dialog>