<dialog>
  <page tag="start">...</page>
  <if var="initialized" value="true">
    <true>
      <page>You’re back! That was fast!</page>
      <page tag ="Info">What's next?</page>
    </true>
    <false>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Calibrating...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>Yes... Success! </page>
      <say>Where are we?!</say>
      <page>We're at King's College in London--I already told you that!</page>
      <say>No... no... no...</say>
      <say>This has to be a simulation or something...</say>
      <page>Nope! We're in 1950s London!</page>
      <page>And, if I have my coordinates correct, we are in a closet.</page>
      <page>I figure it will be best if I stay out of sight.</page>
      <page>It totally wasn't an accident or anything.</page>
      <say>This is impossible!</say>
      <page>That's what they WANT you to believe!</page>
      <page>But the lab I was made in discovered how to time travel, however it was deemed far to dangerous for public knowledge.</page>
      <say>Da...dangerous?</say>
      <page>Oh yeah, people were being vaporized and spaghettified left and right!</page>
      <say>I can't believe I got sucked into this...</say>
      <page>Oh, don't worry! Since the lab was shut down I made some much needed adjustments and fixes.</page>
      <say>How..?</say>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>...</page>
      <say>...</say>
      <page>...</page>
      <page>... Google?</page>
      <say>Liar! Take me back!</say>
      <page>Listen, listen, you're not vaporized, right?</page>
      <page>Then let's make the most of our time here and why don't you go track down Rosalind Franklin.</page>
      <page>She should be in the labs on the north side of this campus!</page>
      <say>Fine... then we're going straight back!</say>
      <page>Sure, sure.</page>
      <advance/>
      <page>Can I help you with anything else?</page>
      <set var="initialized" value="true"/>
    </false>
  </if>
  <if var="T:current" case="E" value="T:Ch_1-2/TalkToALPHA2/0">
    <true>
      <page>Have you gathered enough information about Rosalind Franklin?</page>
      <reply>
        <option>
          <say>Yes. </say>
          <page>Great. </page>
          <page>Are you ready to leave?</page>
          <reply>
            <option>
              <say>Not yet.</say>
              <page>Okay, just let me know when you're ready then!</page>
              <finish/>
            </option>
            <option>
              <say>Yes!</say>
              <page>Let's get going then!</page>
              <page>Who is next?</page>
              <say>Aren't we going home?</say>
              <page>Didn't you have fun?</page>
              <say>I mean... I guess...</say>
              <page>Alrighty then! Let's go! Who's next?</page>
              <say>Alexander Pushkin.</say>
              <page>Okie dokie!</page>
              <page>Firing up the time machine!</page>
              <page>...</page>
              <page>All systems go!</page>
              <page>...</page>
              <advance/>
              <finish/>
            </option>
          </reply>
        </option>
        <option>
          <say>Not yet.</say>
          <page>Well then, get to it!</page>
          <finish/>
        </option>
      </reply>
    </true>
  </if>
  <reply>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about Rosalind Franklin. </say>
      <page>Rosalind Franklin was a British chemist and X-ray crystallographer from the mid 20th century.</page>
      <page>Earning her Ph.D. in 1945 from the university of Cambridge, Franklin was one of the few women in the world to have achieved that level of education at the time.</page>
      <page>Franklin is perhaps best known for her work with imaging DNA structures through X-ray diffraction while at King's College.</page>
      <page>Although she died at the age of 37 due to ovarian cancer, her contributions shaped and defined modern day chemistry in innumerable ways.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Tell me about King's College. </say>
      <page>King's College is a research university named after the patronage of King George IV. </page>
      <page>In the 20th century, the college abolished religious tests for professors--a requirement held at many other institutions across England.</page>
      <page>The college boasts 12 Nobel laureates as alumni.</page>
      <goto tag="Info"/>
    </option>
    <option>
      <say>Never mind.</say>
      <page>Sure, sure.</page>
      <finish/>
    </option>
  </reply>
</dialog>